[
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為sa?",
    "choice1": "と",
    "choice2": "つ",
    "choice3": "そ",
    "choice4": "さ",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為shi?",
    "choice1": "す",
    "choice2": "た",
    "choice3": "て",
    "choice4": "し",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為su?",
    "choice1": "さ",
    "choice2": "す",
    "choice3": "つ",
    "choice4": "そ",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為se?",
    "choice1": "せ",
    "choice2": "て",
    "choice3": "し",
    "choice4": "と",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為so?",
    "choice1": "ち",
    "choice2": "そ",
    "choice3": "し",
    "choice4": "て",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ta?",
    "choice1": "て",
    "choice2": "ち",
    "choice3": "た",
    "choice4": "せ",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為chi?",
    "choice1": "さ",
    "choice2": "し",
    "choice3": "す",
    "choice4": "ち",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為tsu?",
    "choice1": "せ",
    "choice2": "し",
    "choice3": "つ",
    "choice4": "て",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為te?",
    "choice1": "て",
    "choice2": "そ",
    "choice3": "た",
    "choice4": "つ",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為to?",
    "choice1": "と",
    "choice2": "し",
    "choice3": "つ",
    "choice4": "そ",
    "answer": 1
  }
]